Guide to the George Nicolau Papers WAG.250
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Inventory, 1
  - United Airlines / Association of Flight Attendants (Air Wisconsin, Remedy) (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - United Airlines / Association of Flight Attendants (DEN 31-99; Kinlaw-Wells) (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - United Airlines / Association of Flight Attendants (MEC 1-03) (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - United Airlines / Association of Flight Attendants (MEC 9-96) (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - United Airlines / Association of Flight Attendants (MEC 13-95) (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - United Airlines / Association of Flight Attendants (MEC 13-04; Pension Contribution) (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - United Airlines / Association of Flight Attendants (DEN 29-98; Meade) (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - United Airlines / Association of Flight Attendants (Montano, SFT 119-01) (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - United Airlines / Association of Flight Attendants (Nigro) (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - United Airlines / Association of Flight Attendants (Second Officers) (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - United Airlines / Association of Flight Attendants (SFO 29-99; Tamayo) (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - United Airlines / Air Line Pilots Association (1st Class Travel) (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - United Airlines / Association of Flight Attendants (Denise West) (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - United Airlines / Air Line Pilots Association (91-15) (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - United Airlines / Air Line Pilots Association (91-1; Engelman) (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - United Airlines / Air Line Pilots Association (Hong Kong 88-31) (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - United Airlines / Air Line Pilots Association (Lounges Award) (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - US Air / US Shuttle (Supplemental Award) (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - USA / USS Award (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - US Airways Merger (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - NBA (Birdsong and Edwards) (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - NBA (Birdsong II) (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - NBA (Dwight Davis) (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - NBA (Dorsey v. Rockets) (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - NBA (Alex English) (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - NBA (George Johnson) (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - NBA (Gus Johnson) (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - NBA (J. Jones) (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - NBA (King) (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - NBA (Greg Lee) (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - NBA (Bob Love) (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - NBA (Lewis) (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - NBA (Olive v. San Diego) (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - NBA ( John Shumate) (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - NBA (I. Stallworth) (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - NBA (Webster Decision) (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - NBA (Gus Williams) (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Major Indoor Soccer League / MISLPA (General) (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Major Indoor Soccer League / MISLPA (Goal Keepers Uniforms) (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Major Indoor Soccer League / MISLPA (Right of First Refusal 1988) (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Major Indoor Soccer League Players Association / Baltimore Blast (monies) (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Major Indoor Soccer League Players Association / Baltimore Blast (Kunavac) (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Major Indoor Soccer League Players Association / Baltimore Blast (Uremovich) (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Major Indoor Soccer League Players Association / Baltimore Blast (Paul Wright) (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Major Indoor Soccer League Players Association / Chicago Sting (Spalding) (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Major Indoor Soccer League Players Association / Cleveland Crunch (Bernard James) (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Major Indoor Soccer League / MISLPA (Cleveland / St Louis and Tacoma) (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Major Indoor Soccer League / MISLPA (Cleveland) (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Major Indoor Soccer League / MISLPA (Cleveland Kazemaini) (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Major Indoor Soccer League Players Association / Cleveland (Marinaro) (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Major Indoor Soccer League Players Association / Dallas (Ronnberg) (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Furphy / Kansas City Comets) (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - KC Comets / S. Lee (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - KC Comets / MISLPA (Mitchell) (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - KC Comets / MISLPA (Nanchoff) (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - KC Comets / MISPLA (Wilkey) (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - KC Comets / MISPLA (Parker) (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - MISLPA / Phoenix (Gillett) (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - MISLPA / Phoenix (Stetler / Owcharuk) (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - MISLPA / Phoenix (Albuquerque) (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - MISPLA / San Diego (Ortiz and Cogsville) (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - MISPLA / San Diego (Tabrizi) (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - MISPLA / San Francisco Fog (Rolland) (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - MISPLA / San Francisco Fog (Renery) (Box 11, Folder 65)
  - MISPLA / Tacoma (Ralph Black) (Box 11, Folder 66)
  - MISPLA / Tacoma (Vaccaro) (Box 11, Folder 67)
  - MISPLA / Wichita (Borja) (Box 11, Folder 68)
  - MISPLA / Wichita Wings (Leite) (Box 11, Folder 69)
  - Local 1199/ Beckman Downtown Hospital (1330 0372 80) (Box 11, Folder 70)
  - Local 1199 / Beth Israel 00539 98) (Box 11, Folder 71)
  - Local 1199/ Beth Israel (01326 99) (Box 11, Folder 72)
  - Local 1199/ Beth Israel (209 00) (Box 11, Folder 73)
  - Local 1199/ Beth Israel (568 91) (Box 11, Folder 74)
  - Local 1199/ Beth Israel (1448 98) (Box 11, Folder 75)
  - Local 1199 / Beth Israel (97-97; Prunty) (Box 11, Folder 76)
  - Local 1199 / Beth Israel (612-95) (Box 11, Folder 77)
  - Local 1199 / Brookdale Hospital (949 91) (Box 11, Folder 78)
  - Local 1199 / Brookdale (1593 96) (Box 11, Folder 79)
  - Local 1199/ Bronx-Lebanon Hospital (1528 85) (Box 11, Folder 80)
  - Local 1199 / Hospital for Joint Diseases (Hiring Practices) (Box 11, Folder 81)
  - Local 1199 / Interfaith Medical Center (1693 84) (Box 11, Folder 82)
  - Local 1199 / Interfaith Medical Center (127 97) (Box 11, Folder 83)
  - Local 1199 / Jewish Home and Hospital for the Aged (1272 97) (Box 11, Folder 84)
  - Local 1199 / Lenox Hill Hospital (842 91) (Box 11, Folder 85)
  - Local 1199 / Long Island Jewish Hillside Medical Center (46 84) (Box 11, Folder 86)
  - Local 1199 / Long Island Jewish Hospital (369-83) (Box 11, Folder 87)
  - Local 1199 / Long Island Jewish Medical Center (2060 96) (Box 11, Folder 88)
  - Local 1199 / St. Lukes Roosevelt Hospital (943 96) (Box 11, Folder 89)
  - Local 1199 / Lutheran Hospital (626 72) (Box 11, Folder 90)
  - Local 1199 / Montefiore Medical Center (1273 92) (Box 11, Folder 91)
  - Local 1199 / Mount Sinai Medical Center (1585 92; Sheppard) (Box 11, Folder 92)
  - Local 1199 / North General Hospital (302 93; James) (Box 11, Folder 93)
  - Local 1199 / Interfaith Medical Center (1031 99) (Box 11, Folder 94)
  - Local 1199/ Mt. Sinai Medical Center (1228 97; Anyamesem) (Box 11, Folder 95)
  - Local 1199/ Mt. Sinai Medical Center (1173 97) (Box 11, Folder 96)
  - Local 1199/ Mt. Sinai Medical Center (228 97 Prieto) (Box 11, Folder 97)
  - Local 1199/ Mt. Sinai Medical Center (2081 04) (Box 11, Folder 98)
  - Local 1199/ New York Blood Center (1448 96) (Box 11, Folder 99)
  - Local 1199/ New York Blood Center (1325 99) (Box 11, Folder 100)
  - Local 1199/ New York Blood Center (83 99) (Box 11, Folder 101)
  - Local 1199/ New York Medical Center (Donald Stoltzfus) (Box 11, Folder 102)
  - Local 1199/ United Oddfellow and Rebekah Home (1683 94) (Box 11, Folder 103)
  - Local 1199 / St. Lucks Roosevelt Hospital (2 98) (Box 11, Folder 104)
  - Local 1199 / Home of the Sages of Israel (1991 98) (Box 11, Folder 105)
  - Local 1199 / Southside Hospital (1284-74) (Box 11, Folder 106)
  - Local 102, ILAWU / Armark (Holiday Pay Eligibility) (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Local 102, ILAWU / Armark (McDonald) (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Local 102, ILAWU / Armark (Welch) (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Local 102, ILAWU / Arco (Elmehrath) (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Civil Service Employees Assn. / State of New York (J. Ford) (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Local 102, ILAWU / Classic Carriers (Liverpool) (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Security Unit Employees Council 82 / State of New York (Drug Abuse Council) (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Civil Service Employees Association / State of New York (Dept. of Mental Hygiene; Villegas) (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Civil Service Employees Association / State of New York (G. Farris) (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Civil Service Employees Association / State of New York (Dept. of Mental Hygiene Charles Brown Bronx Psychiatric Center) (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Local 102, ILAWU / C.J.Y. Express (Perry) (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Local 102, ILAWU / Fantastic Services (Brown) (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Local 102, ILAWU / Fantastic Services (Brown) (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Local 102, ILAWU / Excellent Trucking (Sylvester) (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Local 102, ILAWU / Excellent Trucking (Martinez) (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Local 102, ILAWU / Fantastic Service (Shiel) (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Local 102, ILAWU / Felson-Feinberg (Severance Pay Claim) (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Local 102, ILAWU / Guaranty Trucking (Samuels) (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Local 102, ILAWU / Guaranty Trucking (Samuels) (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Local 102, ILAWU / Lucky Apparel Carriers (Brown) (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Local 102, ILAWU / Lucky Apparel Carriers (Charles) (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Local 102, ILAWU / New Deal Delivery Services (Woodley) (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Security Unit Employees, Council 82 / State of New York (Barkley; 91-01-1553) (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Security Unit Employees, Council 82 / State of New York (90-01-1217) (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Patrolmens Benevolent Association / City of New York (3609-90; Carney and Ramirez) (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Police Benevolent Association / City of New York (A2092 & 93-85) (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Patrolmens Benevolent Association / City of New York (A-2259-85) (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Local 102, ILAWU / Rutgers Express (Sweatt) (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Security Unit Employees, Council 82 / State of New York (Mitchell) (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Local 102, ILAWU / Sokols Express (Brown) (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Local 102, ILAWU / Speadmark (Branham and Wilson) (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Local 102, ILAWU / Speadmark (Bryant) (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Local 102, ILAWU / Speadmark (Deas) (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Local 102, ILAWU / Speadmark (Gordon) (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Local 102, ILAWU / Speadmark (Douglas Hall) (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Local 102, ILAWU / Speadmark (Onita Johnson) (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Local 102, ILAWU / Speadmark (Peter Lawson) (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Local 102, ILAWU / Speadmark (Ronald McClary) (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Local 102, ILAWU / Speadmark (Juliet Moore) (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Local 102, ILAWU / Speadmark (Emmanuel Pierre) (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Local 102, ILAWU / Speadmark (Curtis Sammuels) (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Local 102, ILAWU / Speadmark (Rivera and Robinson) (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Local 102, ILAWU / Speadmark (Stead) (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Local 102, ILAWU / Speadmark (Walker) (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Local 102, ILAWU / Speadmark (Withers) (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Local 804, IBT / UPS (578-88) (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Local 804, IBT / UPS (Nazario; 188 89) (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Local 804, IBT / UPS (877-88; Shea) (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Local 804, IBT / UPS (8 90) (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Local 177, IBT / UPS (36 93L; dress code) (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Local 804, IBT / UPS (144, 145 & 146 93L) (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Local 102, ILAWU / TSI City Carriers (Newsome, et al) (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Local 102, ILAWU / Trident Express (Calixte) (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Local 102, ILAWU / Walsh Super Service (Anderson) (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - Local 333, United Marine Division / Bridgeport and Port Jefferson Steamboat Company (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - Local 333, United Marine Division / Bouchard Transportation Company (Barge B-80 Arbitration) (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - Local 333, United Marine Division / Bouchard Transportation Company (Reinstatement of James T. Kelly) (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Local 333, United Marine Division / Bouchard Transportation Company (Fromm) (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - Local 333, United Marine Division / Eklof Marine Corporation (Cedric Feuntes) (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - Local 333, United Marine Division / Eklof Marine Corporation (Probost) (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - Local 333, United Marine Division / Turecamo Maritime Agreement (Box 12, Folder 61)
  - Local 333, United Marine Division / Eklof Marine Corporation Settlement (Box 12, Folder 62)
  - Local 333, United Marine Division / Morania Oil Tanker Corp Settlement Agreement (Box 12, Folder 63)
  - Local 333, United Marine Division / Turecamo Maritime, Inc Settlement Agreement (Box 12, Folder 64)
  - NHL (Belanger / Pittsburgh Penguins) (Box 12, Folder 65)
  - NHL / NHLPA (Comparable Exhibit) (Box 12, Folder 66)
  - NHL (Lemieux / New Jersey Devils) (Box 12, Folder 67)
  - NHL / NHLPA (Compliance with Statistical Data Obligations in Salary Arbitration) (Box 12, Folder 68)
  - NHL (Whalers / Oilers) (Box 12, Folder 69)
  - NHL (Whalers / Oilers ) (Box 12, Folder 70)
  - NHL (Iafrate / Bruins) (Box 12, Folder 71)
  - NHL / NHLPA (Joint Exhibit) (Box 12, Folder 72)
  - NHL (Krutov / Vancouver Hockey Club) (Box 12, Folder 73)
  - NHL (Langevin / NY Islanders) (Box 12, Folder 74)
  - NHL / NHLPA (Average League Salary) (Box 12, Folder 75)
  - NHL (Craig / Dallas / Toronto) (Box 12, Folder 76)
  - NHL/ NHLPA (Minimum Compensation Guarantee) (Box 12, Folder 77)
  - NHL (Norwood / New Jersey Devils) (Box 12, Folder 78)
  - NHL / NYLPA (Anderson, et al. Playoff Bonuses) (Box 12, Folder 79)
  - NHL (Pasek / Minnesota North Stars) (Box 12, Folder 80)
  - NHL (Nedved; St. Louis / Vancouver Equalization Payment) (Box 12, Folder 81)
  - NHL / NHLPA (Pro-ration of certain bonuses) (Box 12, Folder 82)
  - NHL (Ramsey / Buffalo and Pittsburgh) (Box 12, Folder 83)
  - NHL (Samuelsson / Pittsburgh Penguins) (Box 12, Folder 84)
  - NHL / NHLPA (Standard Player Contract Issues Penalty Minutes Bonus) (Box 12, Folder 85)
  - NHL (Taglianetti / Pittsburgh Penguins) (Box 12, Folder 86)
  - NHL (Vernon / Detroit Red Wings) (Box 12, Folder 87)
  - NHL (Alexei Yashin) (Box 12, Folder 88)
  - NHL / International Ice Hockey Federation (Yashin) (Box 12, Folder 89)
  - CWA District 13 and Local 13500 / AT&T (Carson) (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - AT&T / IBEW (Crystal Ciccone) (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - AT&T / CWA (Cornell) (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - AT&T / CWA (Hutchinson) (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - AT&T / CWA (Schwarzmeier) (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - AT&T / CWA (Nickles) (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - AT&T / CWA (Neutrality Pittsburgh) (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - AT&T / CWA (Stratigos) (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - AT&T / CWA (Stewart) (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - AT&T / CWA (!-00-185) (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Bell Atlantic / CWA (Halstead) (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Bell Atlantic / CWA (Walton) (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Verizon Connected Solutions (BACCSI) / IBEW, Local 827 (451 99; Emmolo) (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Bell Atlantic / CWA (Ely) (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Bell Atlantic / CWA (CWA 2-96-5 New Job Title) (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Chesapeake and Potomac Telephone Company of West Virginia / CWA (Morris) (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Lucent Technologies / CWA (Pitts) (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - IBEW / New England Telephone and Telegraph Company (Aluia; 1747-84) (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - IBEW / New England Telephone and Telegraph Company (Bagley) (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - IBEW / New England Telephone and Telegraph Company (Barrett) (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - IBEW / New England Telephone and Telegraph Company (Cookson) (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - IBEW / New England Telephone and Telegraph Company (Hickey); 1383-90) (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - IBEW / New England Telephone and Telegraph Company (Megazzini; 1608 94) (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - IBEW / New England Telephone and Telegraph Company (McAdoo; 2508-86) (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - IBEW / New England Telephone and Telegraph Company (Minichiello) (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - IBEW / New England Telephone and Telegraph Company (Morris 1837-84) (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - IBEW / New England Telephone and Telegraph Company (ORourke; 1028-90) (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - IBEW / New England Telephone and Telegraph Company (1671-77; Transfer of Employees) (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - IBEW / New England Telephone and Telegraph Company (916-86; Weir) (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - NYNEX Corporation / CWA (1-95-027; A-95-036; Abbott) (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - New York Telephone Company / CWA (1-88-198; A-88-126) (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - New York Telephone Company / CWA (Bruen) (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - NYNEX Mobile Communications Company / CWA (1-91-66; A-91-4 NX) (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - New York Telephone Company / CWA (1-83-148; A-83-99) (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - New York Telephone Company / CWA (Hall) (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - NYNEX / CWA (Holst; 1-93-121; A-93-1TR) (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - New York Telephone Company / CWA (Pietz) (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - New York Telephone Company / Telephone Traffic Union (Discharge of M. Newham) (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - New York Telephone Company / CWA (Robinette) (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - New York Telephone Company / CWA (Tullo) (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - New York Telephone Company / CWA (Shift of Tour; A-83-167) (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - New York Telephone Company / CWA (McDuffie; A-87-2739 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - PA Bell / CWA (0448 89J) (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - PA Bell / CWA (101 95; Shoes) (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - PA Bell / CWA (14 300 2247 84 J) (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - PA Bell / CWA (145 95) (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - PA Bell / CWA (512 99; Dunn) (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - PA Bell / CWA (1568 82J; Dress Code) (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - PA Bell / CWA (14300 1703 85J; Dress Code II) (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - PA Bell / CWA (1772 97; Suspensions and non-payment Sick Leave) (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - PA Bell / CWA (284 98 J; Unilateral Imposition of Alcohol and Controlled Substance Testing Policy) (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - PA Bell / CWA (52 98; Simonovich) (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - PA Bell / CWA (Douglas) (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - Verizon / CWA (Wright) (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - Verizon / CWA (Michael) (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - Verizon / CWA (Howard) (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - Verizon / CWA (Quotas) (Box 13, Folder 57)
  - Verizon PA / CWA (13-04-56V; 0041-04; assignment administrators) (Box 13, Folder 58)
  - Verizon PA / CWA (022-04) (Box 13, Folder 59)
  - Verizon PA/ CWA (Flood) (Box 13, Folder 60)
  - Verizon PA / CWA (Torres) (Box 13, Folder 61)
  - Verizon / CWA (Cadillac Arbitrations) (Box 13, Folder 62)
  - Bell Telephone Company of PA / Federation Telephone Workers of PA (Box 13, Folder 63)
  - New York Telephone Company / Union of Telephone Workers (Rosado) (Box 13, Folder 64)
  - Bell Atlantic VA / CWA (Roper) (Box 13, Folder 65)
  - Verizon / IBEW, Local 2213 (Baker) (Box 13, Folder 66)
  - United Telephone Company of New Jersey / CWA (Wilson) (Box 13, Folder 67)
  - CSX Lines, Inc / District No. 1 MEBA (Baxter) (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - District No. 1 MEBA / Central Gulf Lines (M/V Nordic Louisiana) (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - District No. 1 MEBA / MORMAC Marine Enterprises (Maritrans Dispute) (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - District No. 1 MEBA / Farrell Lines (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - District No. 1 MEBA / Marine Transport Lines (Lyons) (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - District No. 1 MEBA / Tanker Service Committee (Tug Barges) (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - District No. 1 MEBA / Marine Transport Lines (Derke) (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - District No. 1 MEBA / Matson Navigation Company (Gamba) (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - District No. 1 MEBA / Matson Navigation Company (Hubner) (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - District No. 1 MEBA / MORMAC Marine Enterprises (Porta-Potty Grievance) (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - District No. 1 MEBA / MORMAC Marine Enterprises (Samolchuk) (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - District No. 1 MEBA / MORMAC Marine Transport (Wojcik) (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - District No. 1 MEBA / Marine Transport Lines (Solomon) (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - District No. 1 MEBA / Marine Transport Lines (Gallagher) (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - NMU Plans / Costal Barge Corporation (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - District No. 1 MEBA; NMU / Tanker Service Corporation (Sperounces) (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - District No. 1 MEBA; NMU / Tanker Service Committee and Marine Service Committee (Marine Index Bureau Reports) (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - District 4 NMU/MEBA / Marine Transport Lines (Marine Reliance) (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - District 4 NMU/MEBA / Marine Transport Lines (Fields) (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - District 4 NMU/MEBA / Marine Transport Lines (Oilers) (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - District No. 1 MEBA / Sea-Land Service (Wage Deferral Dispute) (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - District No. 1 MEBA / Sea-Land Service (Christmas Bonus) (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - District No. 1 MEBA / Sea-Land Service (Smith) (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - New Jersey Bell Telephone / CWA (C. Awkward) (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Bell Atlantic - NJ / IBEW, Local 827 (00453 93S; Watkins) (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - New Jersey Bell Telephone / IBEW, Local 827 (0009 91S; Ackerman) (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - New Jersey Bell Telephone / IBEW, Local 827 (00371 91S; Sten) (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - New Jersey Bell Telephone / IBEW, Local 827 (0096 88S; Pirecki) (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - New Jersey Bell Telephone / IBEW, Local 827 (0153 90S; Boyd) (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Bell Atlantic- NJ / IBEW, Local 827 (00670 92S; Marks) (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - New Jersey Bell Telephone / IBEW, Local 827 (0345 88S; Zabreski) (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - New Jersey Bell Telephone / IBEW, Local 827 (0188 90S; Hernandez) (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - New Jersey Bell Telephone / IBEW, Local 827 (0241 88S; Non-Employee Escorts) (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Verizon, NJ / IBEW, Local 827 (02794; Torres) (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - New Jersey Bell Telephone / IBEW, Local 827 (0297 97S; Compano) (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - New Jersey Bell Telephone / IBEW, Local 827 (00305 91S; Travaille) (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - New Jersey Bell Telephone / IBEW, Local 827 (0323 90S; Hanley) (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - New Jersey Bell Telephone / IBEW, Local 827 (0336 89S; Reilly) (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - New Jersey Bell Telephone / IBEW (0402 87S; Nolan) (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - New Jersey Bell Telephone / IBEW, Local 827 (00415 90S; Muschko) (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - New Jersey Bell Telephone / IBEW, Local 827 (0443 90S; Smreczak) (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - New Jersey Bell Telephone / IBEW, Local 827 (0659-86; Fox) (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Verizon, NJ / IBEW, Local 827 (119 99; E. Post) (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Verizon, NJ / IBEW, Local 827 (00142 01; J. Martorano) (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Verizon, NJ / IBEW, Local 827 (15046 02) (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - New Jersey Bell Telephone / IBEW, Local 827 (1882 85; Johnson) (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - New Jersey Bell Telephone / IBEW, Local 827 (2006 85S; HCP Records Clerks Doing CLA Work) (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - Bell Atlantic NJ / IBEW, Local 827 (00227 97) (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - Verizon Connected Solutions / IBEW, Local 827 (00361 00; Chase) (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - Bell Atlantic NJ / IBEW, Local 827 (00396 93S; Maccar) (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - Verizon, NJ / IBEW, Local 827 (00398 99; Hess) (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - Bell Atlantic-NJ / IBEW, Local 827 (00419 93S; Darrah) (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - Bell Atlantic-NJ / IBEW, Local 827 (0519 90; Retirement Planning Seminar) (Box 14, Folder 53)
  - Verizon, NJ / IBEW, Local 827 (8484 1; Thatcher) (Box 14, Folder 54)
  - New Jersey Bell Telephone / IBEW, Local 827 (0627 86S; Sullivan) New Jersey Bell Telephone / IBEW, Local 827 (1318-71) (Box 14, Folder 55)
  - Verizon NJ / IBEW Local 827 (21837 03; Palma) (Box 14, Folder 56)
  - Actors Equity / Phoenix Theatre (General) (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Actors Equity / Godspell Company and Edgar Lansbury, Joseph Beruh, and Stuart Duncan, as Producers of Godspell (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Actors Equity / Naura Hayden (Be Kind to People Week) (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - AEA / Wulp and Berlind, Producers of Lydie Breeze (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - AEA / Coachlight Dinner Theatre (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - AEA / Theater West (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - CUNY / Adelman (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Margaret Alston) (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Annual Leave) (Box 15, Folder 9)